It's Black History Month, but in this segment, we're taking a different approach than repeating
the same Black History Month talking points, okay? We know you're going to get that elsewhere,
but we want you to get something else here. And this is your moments in Black Hood history,
a tribute to little-known historical facts. Facts is a loose term that originated in the hood.
Circa 1982, the Nike Air Force One was released, but the Black ones would become a force to be
reckoned with. One day, a Black man pulled up to the club in Black forces. Legend has it,
when the tips of his shoes entered the room, everyone took cover, for they knew demon time
was upon them. The man with his forces tied tighter than an alibi whipped two asses in record time,
setting forth the original equalizer. Denzel trained with him. He and his Black Air Forces
left the scene. Each hatter echoed throughout the club. From that moment on, no man has stepped foot
in those shoes, other than for the purpose of not standing in the crowd, not standing for something,
but only to stand on business. Yes, yes, yeah. And that is our Black History Month hood moment,
tribute to Black Air Force Ones. Raise a fist. Not to punch nobody, though.